The rules are simple. You break them, you die...
Carriers is a action, drama, horror film directed by Àlex Pastor.
A deadly virus has spread across the globe.
Contagion is everywhere, no one is safe, and no one can be trusted.
Four friends race through the back roads of the American West on their way to a secluded utopian
beach in the Gulf of Mexico where they could peacefully wait out the pandemic.
Their plans take a grim turn when their car breaks down on an isolated
road starting a chain of events that will seal their fates.
Danny Green, played by Lou Taylor Pucci.
Brian Green, played by Chris Pine.
Bobby, played by Piper Perabo.
Kate, played by Emily VanCamp.
Frank Holloway, played by Christopher Meloni.
Jodie Holloway, played by Kiernan Shipka.
Carriers is a 2009 American post-apocalyptic horror film
written and directed by Àlex and David Pastor.
It stars Lou Taylor Pucci, Chris Pine, Piper Perabo, and Emily VanCamp as four survivors of a
viral pandemic attempting to stay alive amid the looming threat of becoming infected.
Filmed in 2006, it received a limited release in the United States on September 4, 2009,
following Pine's breakout performance in Star Trek earlier that year.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed $5.8 million.
The film explores themes of beach, infection, survival, biohazard, disease.
The tone is dark and emotional and thought_provoking.